

INFO

Na 7ab

7ahra Kirschhlüte

9

Address

Sorögatan 67 164 47 Stockholm



Phone

072-002 42 11



Mail

zahra.kirschblute@hotmail.com

in

Linkedin

https://tinyurl.com/kirschblute



Github

github.com/zahrakirschbluete/

PROFILE

Full Stack Developer with previous experience in both the customer service and marketing departments of two of Sweden's fastest growing and sucessful e-commerces. My interest for coding sparked as a teenager and my current long term ambition is to continously grow as a developer.

TECH STACK

C#, .Net Core, EF Core, MsSql, Blazor, JavaScript, React, Angular, HTML, SCSS, bootstrap and much more. I'm of course more than happy to learn new languages and frameworks in orde

LANGUAGES



SWEDISH



GERMANNative tongue



ZAHRA KIRSCHBLÜTE FULL STACK DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-2021

Meds Apotek AB

Software Developer (intern)

- Developed in various projects using .NET Core, EF Core, Blazor, Blazorise and Azure Devops
- Created intergration and unit test using XUnit
- Set up and tested projects in stage server
- Wrote powershell scripts

Snusbolaget AB

2019-2019

- Customer Service Manager
- · Optimized CS routines
- Set KPIs for the CS department
- · Directly reported to the CLO

Desenio AB

2018-2019

Marketing Coordinator, DACH market

- Had continious contact and successful collaborations with influencers
- Optimized routines to ensure that our influencers get the best possible service

Desenio AB

2017-2019

Senior Customer Service Coordinator, DACH market

- Set routines and upkept world-class customer service to ensure increased sales as a result
- · Worked with SEO to rank higher in search engines

Mcdonald's Tornado

2016-2017

Shift Manager

• Responsible for the daily operations at the restaurant

EDUCATION

2019-2021

Chas Academy:

Full Stack Web Development

Practical programme where we mainly focused on vanilla **JavaScript** and frameworks such as **React**, **Angular** and **NodeJs**. **HTML**, **CSS**, **PHP**, **UX Design**, **agile concepts** and much more were also a part of the programme.

2017-2017

McDonald's Business School:

Shift Manager Course

2015-2016

Stockholm Universiy:

Teacher Programme, German and English

2012-2015

St Eriks Gymnasium, Kungsholmen: Natural Science Programme